If the racist white person, I don't mean the person who is examining his consciousness and so on,
doesn't understand that he or she is also a race, it's also constructed, it's also made,
and it also has some kind of serviceability, but when you take it away, I take your race away.
And there you are, all strung out, and all you've got is your little self.
And what is that? What are you without racism?
Are you any good? Are you still strong? Are you still smart? Are you still like yourself?
I mean, these are the questions. Part of it is, yes, the victim, how terrible it has been for black people.
Yeah, but you don't like that.
I'm not a victim. I refuse to be one.
And the victim is the other person who is morally inferior and who has to hold onto racism.
Of course.
Racism is somehow for his or her own self-esteem and definition.
If you can only be tall because somebody is on their knees, then you have a serious problem.
And my feeling is, white people have a very, very serious problem.
And they should start thinking about what they can do about it.
Take me out of it.
Then give.